http://www.medprotect-inc.com/medprotect-customer-service/medprotect-private-policy

MedProtect, Inc.
Personal Protection Kits (PPE) / Safety & Medical Products
“An OSHA Solution”
Phone: 972.941.9500
Fax: 972.941.9599
E-mail: info@medprotect-inc.com
HOMEback to the
homepageCURRENT NEWS EVENTSCUSTOMER SERVICETERMS AND CONDITIONSPRIVACY POLICYRESOURCESFAQsCONTACT UScontact
Medprotect-IncREGISTER/LOGINLogin / Logout
your accountABOUT USproducts and
protection kitsOUR COMPANYMISSION STATEMENTNEWSLETTER
Search...
You are here: Home
CUSTOMER SERVICE
PRIVACY POLICY
Search By Product Category
Personal Protection KitsBloodborne Pathogens Spill Clean-Up KitsCombination Barrier Protection KitsRespirator Protection Kits and Equipment CPR KitsEmergency Room KitOncology/Chemo Administration KitsHurricane Clean-Up KitsEbola/Lassa Fever Virus Pandemic PPE Safety Products
Search By Industry
AviationLaw EnforcementCorrectional InstitutionsFederal Government AgenciesEducational / SchoolsEMS - Emergency Medical ServicesGeneral OfficeHospitals & Medical ClinicsIndustrialNursing HomesState & Local Government AgenciesTransportationRestaurant / HotelsRetailFuneral Homes
PRIVACY POLICY
We at MedProtect are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of our customer’s personal information. Through this privacy statement, MedProtect wants to assure you of our commitment to privacy and security. Our privacy philosophy is based on the concept of fair information practices. This means we provide our customers with notice of how we manage information so that they can have a more informed understanding of how we operate.
Noticeif we collect information from or about you, we will tell you what information is being collected, how, by whom, and for what purposes.
Choicewe will give you options about how the personal information that you provide us may be used.
Securitywe use recognized industry safeguards to protect customer personal information from unauthorized access or use.
AccessYou will have the opportunity to update your personal information that you have provided to us. We will also take steps to make sure that any updates that are provided are processed in a timely and complete manner.
Customer Service and RecourseWe will tell you how you can contact us regarding our privacy statement and practices.
Linking to Other SitesPlease remember that when you use a link to go from medprotect-inc.com to another Web site, the medprotect-inc.com Site Rules and this Privacy Policy are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Website, including any site that has a link on medprotect-inc.com, is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.
ChoiceWe will give you options about how the personal information that you provide us may be used. Before we use your personal information for any purpose, we will give you choices about whether or not to allow us to engage in that use. We will give you the opportunity to keep us from using or sharing the personal information that you have provided to us for purposes other than to fulfill your request. To exercise this choice, we will allow you to notify us of your preferences during the information collection process. If there are third parties that process MedProtect data, we will require them to hold all personally-identifiable information confidential, and to use our customer information only for the purpose of fulfilling their business obligation. MedProtect does not sell personally identifiable information to third party marketers.
SecurityWe use recognized industry safeguards to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized access or use. We will employ industry recognized security safeguards to protect the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us from loss misuse and unauthorized alteration. If you are required to transmit sensitive information (such as credit information) to us through our Website, we will provide you access to our secure server that allows encryption of your data as it is transmitted to us. We will protect personally identifiable information stored on the site's servers from unauthorized access using commercially available computer security products (e.g., firewalls), as well as carefully developed security procedures and practices.
AccessWe will let you update your personal information that you have provided to us. We will also take steps to make sure that any updates that you provide are processed in a timely and complete manner. If we collect personal information through our sites, we will maintain the information and allow you to update it at any time. We will continue to work on better methods of accessing your information to increase your access to it for update purposes. Note that some MedProtect sites may contain links to other sites that are beyond our control, and that you may want to read that sites' privacy policy before entering information.
Customer Service and RecourseWe will tell you how you can contact us regarding our privacy statement and practices. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our information handling practices, or any other aspects of your privacy and the security of information, please send an email to
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
or call us at 972-941-9500. Our mailing address is: 1900 Preston Rd. Suite 267, Plano, Texas 75093
We retain the flexibility to update this policy. MedProtect may periodically update this policy to describe how new Web features may affect our use of your information and to let you know of new controls and features that we may provide you. MedProtect will NOT apply changes to this policy retroactively to information MedProtect has previously collected.
© 2020 Medprotect-Inc. All Rights Reserved.
